# Mostafa Syam

### Front-End Developer

Highly motivated and experienced Web Developer with a passion for creating intuitive, user-friendly websites and applications. I have extensive experience in developing websites/applications using latest web technologies. My goal is to create aesthetically pleasing applications that meet the client's requirements and exceed their expectations. I am a self-starter and an independent learner, I am confident of my ability to provide the best possible solutions to the client's needs.

mospro@live.com

+20 1555 292 685



Egypt, Cairo



itsmos.netlify.app

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance Front End Developer Mushor

01/2023 - 02/2032

Tasks

- Built a client-facing E-commerce system.
- Connected ~15 dynamic pages to the back-end.
- Implemented search and permissions functionalities in the dashboard.

## Freelance Front End Developer A Plus Plumbing

08/2020 - 09/2020

Tasks

- Redesigned the old website to be more appealing and generate more customers.
- Implemented pixel perfect UI designs.

## Fullstack Developer

Liberty City Roleplay

2020 - 2021

Achievements

Made a web app user control panel to manage in-game assets.

#### Title/Position

Workplace/Company

## Freelance Front End Developer

NTC 2017

NTC Training Center and Human Resources

- Built an informative landing page with events calendar.

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Community Forum

- Created a forums website using Vue 3, with the ability to customize profiles.
- Integrated Firebase datastore and authentication.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Computer Science Bachelor**

Misr University for Science and Technology

2017 - 2021

## **TECHNOLOGIES**



## **SKILLS**

UI Design Implementation: Pixel perfect design implementation with readable & clean code.

Responsive UI: Experienced in designing responsive user interfaces that suit various screen sizes and platforms, providing an optimal user experience.

Consuming APIs: Iv'e used multiple libraries (jquery, axios, fetch) to make ajax requests.

SPA: Creating single-page applications using Vue 3.

Databases: Well-versed in creating and maintaining databases such as Mongodb and MySQL.

GIT: I use version control system everyday.

Accessibility: I strive to develop intuitive, user-friendly designs that comply with the latest accessibility standards.

Making REST API: Ability to create robust, scalable, and secure APIs that adhere to the best practices and standards (nodejs)

#### **LANGUAGES**

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

**Enalish** 

Professional Working Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

